MONICA, WHICH OF ALL
OF THIS KITCHEN STUFF IS MINE?
THIS BOTTLE OPENER.
AND...?
AND IT'S A MAGNET.
GO ON.
LOOK AT THAT.
HOW WEIRD IS THAT?
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE MOVING IN WITH ME
AND YOU HAVE THE ONE THING
I DON'T HAVE.
HUH? IT'S
LIKE, UH...
IN A WAY YOU,
YOU COMPLETE ME.
YOU KNOW?
KITCHEN.
WHAT?
YOU COMPLETE ME KITCHEN, MATEY.
ROSS, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
WHAT?
THAT SHE'S GOING
TO MOVE IN WITH YOU
AND THEN MAYBE
SHE'LL FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU
AND THEN, WHEN SHE FINDS OUT
YOU'RE ALREADY MARRIED
OH, SHE'LL JUST BE HAPPY,
YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE JUST... YOU'RE VERY SAD.
OH... MY... GOD.
I... I SEE WHAT THIS IS.
YOU ARE IN LOVE
WITH RACHEL.
WHAT?!
OF COURSE.
IT ALL ADDS UP.
I MEAN, YOU'RE
OBSESSED WITH HER.
IT'S ALWAYS, "ROSS,
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO ABOUT RACHEL?"
"ROSS, WHY ARE YOU
MOVING IN WITH RACHEL?"
"WHEN ARE YOU
GOING TO CONFESS
YOUR SECRET MARRIAGE
TO RACHEL?"
YOU WANT HER.
NO!
( phone ringing )
UH. OH, SAVED
BY THE BELL.
HELLO?
HEY, RACH,
AREN'T THESE
CANDLESTICKS MINE?
NO, NO, I BOUGHT THOSE.
OH, RIGHT. I FORGOT...
YEAH.
( whispering ):
THAT YOU'RE A LIAR.
Ross:
NO, NO.
THAT'S GREAT.
I'LL BE THERE MONDAY.
AND THANK YOU
AGAIN. OKAY.
UM, THAT WAS THE HEAD
OF THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT
AT "N"... UH, "Y"... UH, "U."
WOW. UH, WHAT...
DID HE... UH, SAY?
WELL, REMEMBER THAT
PAPER I HAD PUBLISHED
LAST YEAR ON SEDIMENT
FLOW RATE? HUH?
THEY LOVED IT.
WELL, WHO WOULDN'T?
I KNOW.
ANYWAY, THEY ASKED ME TO BE
A GUEST LECTURER.
I MEAN, IT'S TEMPORARY,
BUT, IF THEY LIKE ME
IT COULD LEAD
TO A FULL-TIME JOB.
HOW GREAT WOULD THAT LOOK
ON THE MAILBOX, HUH?
PROFESSOR GELLER.
YEAH, PROFESSOR AND MRS.
AND MRS.?
UH...
OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW,
YOU AND ROSS ARE
STILL MARRIED.
WHAT?!
JUST KIDDING.
OH, GOD!
CAN YOU IMAGINE?!
NO!
SAVED YOUR ASS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HI.
( dejected tone ):
OH, WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
WELL... YOU KNOW
THAT PSYCHIC I SEE?
YEAH.
WELL, SHE TOLD ME THAT I'M GOING
TO DIE THIS WEEK, SO I'M KIND OF
BUMMED ABOUT THAT.
WHAT?
YEAH, AND I KNOW
YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW
A LOT ABOUT PSYCHIC READINGS
BUT THAT ONE IS PRETTY MUCH
THE WORST ONE YOU CAN GET.
PHOEBE,
THAT'S CRAZY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE WOULD SAY THAT TO YOU.
YEAH, HONEY, YOU DON'T
BELIEVE HER, DO YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE, YOU KNOW,
SAID THAT I'D HAVE TRIPLETS.
BUT SHE ALSO SAID
ONE OF THEM WOULD BE BLACK.
JUST OUT OF CURIOSITY,
DID SHE TELL YOU
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO GO?
NO, 'CAUSE SHE DIDN'T TELL ME
I WAS GOING TO DIE
TILL THE VERY END
OF THE SESSION
AND I WAS NOT GOING TO WASTE
A WHOLE OTHER HOUR THERE.
I MEAN, I'VE ONLY GOT
A WEEK LEFT, YOU KNOW?
I'VE REALLY GOT
TO START LIVING NOW.
HEY, EVERYONE.
OH, HI.
HEY, UH, WELL, TODAY'S
MY FIRST LECTURE
AND I KIND OF WANTED
TO TRY IT OUT ON YOU GUYS.
DO YOU MIND?
NO, THAT'D BE GREAT.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
SURE.
OKAY.
( sighs )
( humming nervously )
( monotone voice ):
"THERE ARE THREE
PRIMARY THEORIES
"CONCERNING SEDIMENT FLOW RATE.
"EACH OF THESE THEORIES CAN
BE FURTHER SUBCATEGORIZED..."
OH, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHAT'S
GOING TO KILL ME.
"SUBCATEGORIES:
"THE FIRST
OF THESE SUBCATEGORIES...
Joey:
UH, ROSS.
ARE THERE, UH, ARE THERE NAKED
CHICKS ON THAT PIECE OF PAPER?
NO. WHY?
WELL, I JUST NEVER SEEN
A GUY STARE SO HARD
AT A PIECE OF PAPER THAT
DIDN'T HAVE NAKED CHICKS ON IT.
OH.
OKAY.
"THERE ARE THREE...
"PRIMARY THEORIES...
"CONCERNING SEDIMENT FLOW RATE.
"EACH OF THESE
"THEORIES CAN BE
FURTHER SUBCATEGORIZED...
"INTO...
WHY DON'T YOU OPEN
WITH A JOKE?
OPEN WITH A JOKE?
IT'S A UNIVERSITY,
NOT A COMEDY CLUB.
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE.
HOLD THE PHONE.
YOU'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT CHUCKLES UNIVERSITY?
OKAY.
WE'RE KIDDING.
COME ON.
ROSS, HEY,
YOU KNOW
WHAT MIGHT MAKE IT LESS BORING?
THANK YOU.
SOME, UM, SOME VISUAL AIDS.
OOH-OOH! YOU KNOW
WHAT'S A GOOD VISUAL AID?
PLEASE DON'T SAY "NAKED CHICKS."
WHY NOT?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I BOTHER TO EVEN TALK
TO YOU GUYS ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
I'M JUST GOING TO DO IT
ON MY OWN WITH NO NAKED CHICKS.
THAT'S THE WAY I DID IT
UNTIL I WAS 19.
HI.
HEY.
ANY GOOD MAIL?
YES. YOU GOT SOMETHING
FROM THE SCREEN ACTORS GUILD.
OOH. IT'S PROBABLY
A RESIDUAL CHECK.
HEY, CAN YOU OPEN IT FOR ME?
I GOT A...
"BENEFITS LAPSED."
HMM. THAT'S WEIRD.
I DON'T REMEMBER BEING
IN A MOVIE CALLED
"BENEFITS LAPSED."
IT'S NOT A CHECK.
THEY'RE SAYING YOUR HEALTH
INSURANCE EXPIRED BECAUSE...
YOU DIDN'T
WORK ENOUGH LAST YEAR.
LET ME SEE THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
THIS SUCKS.
WHEN I HAD INSURANCE,
I COULD GET HIT BY A BUS OR...
OR CATCH ON FIRE, YOU KNOW?
AND IT WOULDN'T MATTER.
NOW I GOT TO BE CAREFUL?
I'M SORRY, MAN.
THERE'S NEVER A GOOD
TIME TO HAVE TO...
STOP CATCHING ON FIRE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL... I GUESS
I GOT TO GO GET A JOB.
I'M GOING TO GO SEE MY AGENT.
OKAY, AND MAKE SURE
TO LOOK BOTH WAYS
BEFORE YOU CROSS THE STREET.
( sarcastically ):
MAKE SURE TO LOOK BOTH WAYS
BEFORE YOU CROSS THE STREET.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
OH, IT'S SO EXHAUSTING
WAITING FOR DEATH.
OH, BY THE WAY,
DO YOU THINK...
( gasping )
PHEEBS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WAS PREPARING YOU
FOR MY DE...
DIDN'T YOU THINK I WAS DEAD?
DID THAT NOT COME OFF?
NO. YEAH,
SCARED THE HELL OUT OF ME.
I THOUGHT
WE'D LOST YOU FOREVER.
PHEEBS, YOU WANT TO LIE DOWN?
YEAH. THANKS.
AND, LISTEN,
CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
CAN YOU JUST, UH, WAKE ME UP
IN A COUPLE HOURS--
YOU KNOW, IF YOU CAN?
MONICA...
DID-DID YOU TAKE THESE BACK?
NO, NO.
I JUST... I LIKED THEM SO MUCH
THAT I WENT OUT
AND BOUGHT SOME FOR MYSELF.
OH. YEAH, THEY'RE
REALLY GREAT, AREN'T THEY?
I LOVE THEM.
YEAH.
NICE TRY.
HELLO.
HEY. HOW'D THE LECTURE GO?
IT WENT GREAT.
AND I DIDN'T NEED ANY JOKES
OR NAKED CHICKS EITHER.
WOW. THAT'S GREAT, ROSS.
I'M SORRY WE WEREN'T
MORE SUPPORTIVE BEFORE.
I KNEW ALL I HAD TO DO WAS LET
THE MATERIAL SPEAK
FOR ITSELF, HUH?
EVERYONE'S ALL, UH
"ROSS, YOU HAVE TO BE
FUNNY AND SEXY."
WELL, I PROVED THEM WRONG.
AND NOW,
I'M GOING TO PASS THE NEWS ON
TO JOEY AND CHANDLER.
THAT YOU'RE NOT FUNNY
OR SEXY?
THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY, ESTELLE,
LISTEN...
WELL, WELL, WELL.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
SO YOU CAME BACK, HUH?
THEY THINK THEY CAN DO BETTER
BUT THEY ALL COME
CRAWLING BACK TO ESTELLE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I NEVER LEFT YOU.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN MY AGENT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, WELL.
NO HARM, NO FOUL.
LOOK, ESTELLE...
YOU GOT TO GET
ME SOME WORK.
I LOST MY
HEALTH INSURANCE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THING WE GOT TO DO--
DAMAGE CONTROL.
WHY?
WELL, I THINK, UH...
SOMEONE OUT THERE...
MAY HAVE BEEN BAD-MOUTHING
YOU ALL OVER TOWN.
THAT BASTARD!
HI.
( in strained voice ):
HEY.
SO ESTELLE
LINED UP A BUNCH OF AUDITIONS
FOR ME TOMORROW
AND I'LL HAVE MY HEALTH
INSURANCE BACK IN NO TIME.
THAT'S GREAT, BUT...
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
ON THE TOILET RIGHT NOW?
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
WELL, I GOT THIS BLINDING PAIN
IN MY STOMACH
WHEN I WAS
LIFTING WEIGHTS BEFORE
AND THEN I, UH, PASSED OUT
AND, UH, I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO STAND UP SINCE.
( weak chuckle )
BUT, UH, I DON'T THINK
IT'S ANYTHING SERIOUS, YOU KNOW?
THIS SOUNDS LIKE A HERNIA.
YOU HAVE TO...
YOU GO TO THE DOCTOR.
NO WAY. OKAY, LOOK, IF I'M GOING
TO GO TO THE DOCTOR FOR ANYTHING
IT'S GOING TO BE FOR THIS THING
STICKING OUT OF MY STOMACH.
( groaning )
THAT'S A HERNIA.
WHY'D I HAVE TO START
WORKING OUT AGAIN?
DAMN YOU 15s!
WELL, WE'RE A LITTLE EARLY.
THE LECTURE DOESN'T END
FOR 15 MINUTES.
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, WE
COULD SNEAK IN AND WATCH.
YEAH. OH, HEY, LOOK.
THERE'S SOME
KAPPA KAPPA DELTAS.
I WAS A KAPPA.
HEY, SISTERS.
WOW. WE REALLY ARE BITCHES.
( speaking with confident
British accent )
RIGHT. SO WHEN RIGBY
GOT HIS SAMPLES
BACK FROM THE LABORATORY
HE MADE A STARTLING DISCOVERY.
WHAT HE BELIEVED TO BE IGNEOUS
WAS, IN FACT, SEDIMENTARY.
IMAGINE HIS CONSTERNATION
WHEN...
OH, BLOODY 'ELL.
Monica:
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
LOOK, I WAS NERVOUS.
YOU GUYS HAD ME ALL WORRIED
I WAS GOING TO BE BORING.
I GOT UP THERE AND THEY WERE
ALL, LIKE, STARING AT ME.
I OPENED MY MOUTH
AND THIS BRITISH ACCENT
JUST CAME OUT.
YEAH, AND NOT
A VERY GOOD ONE.
WILL YOU PLEASE...?
DR. GELLER, KURT RATHMAN.
I'M A PROFESSOR IN
THE PALEONTOLOGY
DEPARTMENT HERE.
DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT TO
TALK ABOUT YOUR LECTURE?
( British accent ):
I'M SORRY, I'VE GOT
PLANS WITH MY SISTER.
( Irish accent ):
MONICA GELLER-R-R-R....
RIGHT. WILL YOU EXCUSE
US FOR ONE MOMENT?
( normal ):
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
( normal):
OH, YOU CAN HAVE AN
ACCENT, BUT I CAN'T?
( Irish ):
TOP O' THE MORNIN'
TO YE, LADDIES!
WILL YOU JUST
PLEASE STOP?
( Indian accent ):
YES, YES, BOMBAY IS
VERY, VERY NICE
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
( grunting )
( sobbing )
HEY, WILL YOU GRAB ME
A CRULLER?
( whining )
SIT DOWN!
WILL YOU GO TO THE HOSPITAL?
DUDE, HERNIA OPERATIONS COST,
LIKE... A LOT, PROBABLY, OKAY?
BESIDES, IT'S GETTING DARKER
AND MORE PAINFUL.
THAT MEANS IT'S HEALING.
LOOK, I WILL LOAN YOU
THE MONEY.
JUST GO TO THE HOSPITAL,
AND LET'S JUST GET THAT THING...
PUSHED BACK IN?
THANK YOU, BUT IT WOULD
TAKE ME FOREVER
TO PAY YOU THAT MONEY BACK,
AND...
I DON'T WANT THAT
HANGING OVER MY HEAD, OKAY?
AND BESIDES, AS SOON AS
MY INSURANCE KICKS IN
I CAN GET ALL THE FREE
OPERATIONS I WANT, OKAY?
I THINK I'LL PROBABLY START WITH
THAT LASER EYE SURGERY THING.
HEY...
HEY.
( groaning )
HEY...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, JOEY'S GOT
A REALLY BAD HERNIA
BUT IT'S NOTHING THAT A LITTLE
LASER EYE SURGERY WON'T FIX,
LOOK, I'M TELLING YOU--
IF I PUT MY HAND
ON MY STOMACH RIGHT HERE
IT DOESN'T HURT THAT BAD.
HEY! MAYBE YOU'LL DIE.
CHANDLER, I'M SCARED.
NO, WE CAN GO
TOGETHER!
JUST DON'T WAIT TOO LONG,
THOUGH, OKAY?
'CAUSE I'M OUT OF HERE
SOMETIME BEFORE FRIDAY.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
NO, NO, IT'LL BE FUN.
WE CAN COME BACK
AND WE CAN HAUNT THESE GUYS.
GIVE ME THEM!
NO! THEY ARE MINE!
YOU STOLE THEM FROM ME!
GIVE ME THEM!
YOU JUST WANT TO EACH
TAKE ONE?
YEAH, THAT SEEMS FAIR--
WE NEVER USE THEM.
LOOK, I REALLY NEED
SOME HELP, OKAY?
WHY, WHY DID I HAVE TO SPEAK
IN A BRITISH ACCENT?
WHAT DO I DO?
WELL... WHY DON'T
YOU PHASE IT OUT?
YEAH, PHASE THE ACCENT OUT--
PEOPLE WILL THINK THAT,
YOU'RE, YOU KNOW
JUST ADJUSTING TO LIFE
IN AMERICA.
Rachel:
YEAH, COME ON, ROSS--
NO ONE'LL EVEN NOTICE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE PROBABLY NOT
EVEN LISTENING TO YOU.
THEY'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME?
OF COURSE THEY'RE LISTENING
TO YOU.
EVERYBODY LISTENS TO YOU.
MONICA, UH,
YOU REALLY THINK I SHOULD TRY
THIS "PHASING OUT" THING?
I THINK YOU LOOK FINE.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
OKAY.
( groaning )
HEY, TIMMY...
I'VE GOT A...
SURPRISE... FOR YOU.
HOLD IT, I'M SORRY.
THE SURPRISE IS
A NEW SWING SET.
IF YOU COULD PLAY IT
A LITTLE LESS INTENSE?
YEAH, SURE. NO PROBLEM.
UH, JUST HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
( groaning )
HEY, TIMMY...
I'VE GOT A SURPRISE
FOR YOU.
OH, MY GOD!
...SO THAT'S WHY I FEED MY DOG
PURINA ONE.
PICK UP A BAG TODAY.
THAT'S WHERE YOU
PICK UP THE BAG.
EXACTLY.
NO, THE LINE IS "PICK UP A BAG,"
SO YOU NEED TO PICK UP THE BAG.
OR...
I COULD JUST POINT TO IT, HUH?
"BLAH-BLAH-BLAH, PURINA ONE.
POINT TO A BAG TODAY."
I DIDN'T GET IT, DID I?
NO.
YEAH, OKAY.
HI. I'M, UH, JOEY TRIBBIANI.
I'M HERE TO AUDITION FOR "MAN."
( groaning )
YOU MEAN "DYING MAN"?
YES!
OKAY, COME ON--
DO IT ONE MORE TIME.
REALLY? REALLY?
YES!
OKAY.
( Scottish accent ):
HELLO, ROSS?
THIS IS DR. McNEELY
FROM THE FAKE ACCENT UNIVERSITY.
WE'D LIKE YOU TO COME ONBOARD
WITH US FULL-TIME.
( squealing )
HEY!
LISTEN TO THIS--
MY READING WAS WRONG;
I'M NOT GOING TO DIE.
REALLY? HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE MY PSYCHIC IS DEAD.
SHE MUST HAVE READ
THE CARDS WRONG.
OH... WELL, I'M SORRY.
EH, BETTER HER THAN ME.
HEY, LET'S BAKE COOKIES!
LISTEN, I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU GOT THE PART.
( groaning )
BUT ARE YOU SURE
YOU CAN DO THIS?
YEAH! AND, HEY, MAN,
THANKS FOR COMING WITH ME.
AND THANKS AGAIN
FOR HELPING ME TAKE A SHOWER.
NOW, IS THAT
"NEVER TALKING
ABOUT IT AGAIN"?
HIYA.
HEY, JOEY, WE'RE
READY FOR YOU.
UH, JOEY, THIS IS ALEX.
HE'S GOING TO BE PLAYING
YOUR SON.
HI, ALEX.
AND, UH, AS YOU CAN SEE,
MY HANDS-- NOT IN MY PANTS.
OKAY...
ALL RIGHT, UH, ALEX,
NOW, WHEN JOEY SAYS HIS LINE
"TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOUR MAMA, SON"--
THAT'S YOUR CUE TO CRY.
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO THIS.
SCENE FIVE, TAKE ONE.
AND... ACTION!
TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOUR MAMA, SON.
COME ON, SON...
YOUR MAMA'S GOOD PEOPLE.
CUT!
ALEX, REMEMBER...
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO CRY.
CAN YOU CRY FOR US
THIS TIME?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, FROM THE TOP.
SCENE FIVE, TAKE TWO.
TAKE 36 IS UP.
Director:
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
TRY THIS AGAIN.
ARE YOU READY, JOE?
UH, ONE THING--
IS IT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU
IF I... IF I SCREAM
RIGHT UP UNTIL YOU
SAY "ACTION"?
UH, SURE.
( screaming )
ACTION!
TAKE GOOD CARE
OF YOUR MAMA, SON.
CUT!
( screaming )
I'M SORRY.
HEY, HEY, JOE, WHY DON'T
YOU LIFT UP YOUR SHIRT?
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS,
KIDDO.
( crying )
WE HAVE HIM CRYING, JOHN!
ROLL THE DAMN CAMERAS!
( phone rings )
( ringing )
HELLO?
HELLO, IS ROSS THERE?
UH, NO, HE'S NOT.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
Yes. This is Russell,
Ross's divorce lawyer.
JUST TELL HIM THAT SINCE
I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HIM
I ASSUME HE'S DECIDED
TO GIVE THE MARRIAGE A TRY.
ROSS GOT MARRIED AGAIN?
( gasping )
NO!
ALL RIGHT, KEEP GOING.
WE ARE PHASING THE ACCENT OUT--
PHASING IT OUT.
( unaccented ):
SO WITHOUT RETESTING THE
RESULTS IN THE LA-BOR-ATORY
( light accent ):
THE TEAM WOULD NEVER
HAVE I-DENTI-FIED...
( unaccented ):
THE INITIAL ERRORS IN THEIR...
( accent ):
CARBON-DATING ANAL-YSIS.
( unaccented ):
WERE THERE ANY QUESTIONS
AT THIS POINT?
YES?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOUR ACCENT?
( accent ):
COME AGAIN.
WHAT'S-WHAT'S THIS NONSENSE?
( nervous tittering )
( unaccented ):
ALL RIGHT, I'M-I'M NOT ENGLISH.
I'M FROM LONG ISLAND.
I WAS REALLY NERVOUS,
AND THE ACCENT JUST, UH...
JUST CAME OUT.
( accent ):
I'M SORRY.
( unaccented ):
SO, IF WE COULD JUST
GET BACK TO THE LECTURE.
UM... WERE THERE ANY QUESTIONS?
ABOUT PALEONTOLOGY?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE A GOOD FIRST IMPRESSION.
OBVIOUSLY, I SCREWED UP.
BUT WHAT YOU GUYS THINK OF ME
IS REALLY IMPORTANT
BECAUSE I'M-I'M HOPING
TO GET A PERMANENT JOB HERE.
SO IF YOU JUST GIVE ME
ANOTHER CHANCE
TO MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION...
ROSS! ARE YOU CRAZY?!
I AM STILL YOUR WIFE?!
WHAT, WERE YOU JUST
NEVER GOING TO TELL ME?!
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG
WITH YOU?!!
OH! I COULD JUST
KILL YOU!
( heavy accent ):
WELL, 'ELLO, RACHEL!
SO, YOU'VE REALLY
DONE THIS BEFORE?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU JUST TAKE A BIG,
BIG SWING, OKAY?
NOW, DON'T HOLD BACK.
OKAY.
HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'RE JUST CELEBRATING
THAT JOEY GOT HIS
HEALTH INSURANCE BACK.
OH, ALL RIGHT.